A Guide to the Papers of the Tucker, Harrison and Smith Families, 1790-1940
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Eliza Tucker and Gessner Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1847 Jan. 15, ALS (Box 6)
- T. C. Ferreter to J. H. Smith 1847 Jan. 21, ALS (Box 6)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1847 Feb. 11, ALS (Box 6)
- George Tucke to Mary Stuart Harrison 1847 Feb. 11, ALS (Box 6)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Lelia Tucker 1847 Feb. 12, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Lelia Tucker 1847 Feb. [30?], ALS (Box 6)
- Ellen Lewis to Mary Lelia Tucker [1847] March 6, ALS (Box 6)
- Gessner and Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Margaret (Harrison) Stevens 1847 March 22, ALS (Box 6)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1847 April 5, ALS (Box 6)
- Gessner Harrison to Peachey Rush Harrison 1847 April 5, ALS (Box 6)
- George Tucker to Mary Lelia Tucker 1847 May 4, ALS (Box 6)
- Gessner Harrison to Dr. Peachey Harrison 1847 May 20, ALS (Box 6)
- Margaret Harrison Stevens to Mary Jane Harrison 1847 June 30, ALS (Box 6)
- Dr. Peachey Harrison to Mary Stewart Harrison 1847 July 5, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Lelia Tucker 1847 July 14, ALS (Box 6)
- Margaret (Harrison) Stevens to Mary Jane Harrison 1847 July 15, ALS (Box 6)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. (Harrison) Stevens 1847 July 16, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Mary Lelia Tucker 1847 July 17, ALS (Box 6)
- Margaret Harrison Stevens to William G. Stevens and Mary Jane Harrison 1847 July 21, ALS (Box 6)
- Mary Lelia Tucker to niece Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1847 July 21, ALS (Box 6)
- Margaret (Harrison) Stevens to Mary Jane Harrison 1847 July 26, ALS (Box 6)
- Dr. Peaachey and Mary Jane Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1847 July 30, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Lelia Tucker [1847 July], ALS (Box 6)
- John H. Stevens to [Margaret F. Stevens] 1847 Aug. 3, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Lelia Tucker 1847 Aug. 9, ALS (Box 6)
- [Peachey Rush Harrison] to Mary F. (Rodes) Harrison 1847 Aug. 11, ALS (Box 6)
- Eliza Tucker Harrison to Dr. Gessner Harrison 1847 Sept. 6, ALS (Box 6)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. (Harrison) Stevens 1847 Sept. 8, ALS (Box 6)
- Ellen Lewis to Mary Lelia Tucker [1847] Sept. 13, ALS (Box 6)
- Eliza Tucker Harrison to Mary Lelia Tucker 1847 Sept. 30, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Lelia Tucker 1847 Oct. 4, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1847 Oct. 10, ALS (Box 6)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1847 Nov. 11, AL (Box 6)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Lelia Tucker 1847 Nov. 13, ALS (Box 6)
- Margaret Harrison Stevens to Mary Jane Harrison 1847 Nov. 17, ALS (Box 6)
- [?] Wicks to Caroline E. Harrison 1847 Nov. 28, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Lelia Tucker 1847 Dec. 3, ALS (Box 6)
- Margaret (Harrison) Stevens to Mary Jane Harrison 1847 Dec. 9, ALS (Box 6)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Margaret Harrison Stevens (Mrs. Wm. G. Stevens) 1847 Dec. 23, ALS (Box 6)
- Mary W. Ross to Mary Lelia Tucker 1847 [?] 10, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Lelia Tucker ca. 1847, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Mary Stuart Harrison 1848 Jan. 1, ALS (Box 6)
- Margaret Harrison Stevens to Mary Jane Harrison 1842 Jan. 2, ALS (Box 6)
- Caroline E. Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1848 Jan. 14, ALS (Box 6)
- Eliza Tucker Harrison to Mary Lelia Tucker 1848 Jan. 18, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1848 Feb. 2, ALS (Box 6)
- Gessner Harrison to Dr. Peachey Harrison 1848 Feb. 5, ALS (Box 6)
- George Tucker to Mary Lelia Tucker 1848 Feb. 16, ALS (Box 6)
- Dr. Peachey Harrison to the Rev. G. W. Israel 1848 Feb. 17, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Lelia Tucker 1848 Feb. 23, ALS (Box 6)
- Mary Stuart Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1848 Feb. 28, ALS (Box 6)
- Anna M. Lomax to Maria (Tucker) Rives (MRs. George Rives) [1848?] March 8, ALS (Box 6)
- Gessner Harrison to Professor Tutwiler 1848 March 22, ALS (Box 6)
- Gessner Harrison to Dr. Peachey Harrison 1848 April 9, ALS (Box 6)
- Mary Rodes to Dr. Peachey Rush Harrison 1848 April 15, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Lelia Tucker 1848 April 22, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1848 April 27, ALS (Box 6)
- [Peachey Rush Harrison] to his Aunt [?] 1848 April 29, ALS (Box 6)
- Gessner Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison [1848 April], ALS (Box 6)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1848 May 3, ALS (Box 6)
- May Rodes to Dr. Peachey Rush Harrison, Jr. (fragment) 1848 May 11, ALS (Box 6)
- (fragment) Gessner Harrison to Peachey Rush Harrison 1848 May 14, ALS (Box 6)
- Mary W. Ross to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1848 May 17, ALS (Box 6)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Lelia Tucker 1848 June 10, ALS (Box 6)
- [Colonel Kinney] to Gessner Harrison 1848 June 26, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Lelia Tucker 1848 July 15, ALS (Box 6)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Harrison 1848 Aug. 14, ALS (Box 6)
- Edward Buckey Smith to Summerfield Smith 1848 Aug. 22, ALS (Box 6)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Harrison 1848 Oct. 20, ALS (Box 6)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1848 Nov. 25, ALS (Box 6)
- Gessner and Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Harrison 1848 Nov. 29, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Mary Stuart Harrison 1848 Dec. 7, ALS (Box 6)
- (fragment) Mary Jane Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1848 Dec. 18, AL (Box 6)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison [1848], ALS (Box 6)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Mary Stuart Harrison 1849 Jan. 9, ALS (Box 6)
- Margaret (Harrison) Stevens to Caroline E. Harrison 1849 Feb. 2, ALS (Box 6)
- William G. Stevens to Caroline E. Harrison 1849 Feb. 3, ALS (Box 6)
- Peachey Gessner Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1849 Feb. 8, LS (Box 6)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1849 Feb. 16, ALS (Box 6)
- William G. Stevens to Caroline E. Harrison 1849 Feb. 23, ALS (Box 6)
- Gessner Harrison to Peachey Rush Harrison 1849 Feb. 27, ALS (Box 6)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1849 Feb. 28, ALS (Box 6)
- Mary Stuart Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1849 March 1, ALS (Box 6)
- Caroline E. Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison (Mrs. Peachey Harrison) 1849 March 9, ALS (Box 6)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1849 March 13, ALS (Box 6)
- Erasmus G. Hamilton to Matthew G. and Eliza P. Hamilton 1849 March 26, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1849 March 30, ALS (Box 6)
- Gessner and Maria Carter Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1849 April 2, ALS (Box 6)
- Charles Carter Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison and Maria Carter Harrison 1849 April 4, ALS (Box 6)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Mary Stuart Harrison 1849 April 11, ALS (Box 6)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Frances M. Stuart 1849 April 11, ALS (Box 6)
- Francis H. Smith to Ellen E. Smith (Mrs. D. G. Smith) 1849 April 28, ALS (Box 7)
- Mary F. Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1849 May 3, ALS (Box 7)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1849 May 21, ALS (Box 7)
- Mary F. Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1849 May 29, ALS (Box 7)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallce) to Mary Jane Harrison 1849 June 1, ALS (Box 7)
- Caroline E. Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1849 June 5, ALS (Box 7)
- William G. Stevens and Mary Jane Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1849 June 8, ALS (Box 7)
- T. F. Tebbs to Francis H. Smith 1849 June 15, ALS (Box 7)
- Erasmus G. Hamilton to Ellen E. (Hamilton) Smith 1849 June 28, ALS (Box 7)
- Sarah Conway to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1849 July 2, ALS (Box 7)
- Caroline E. Harrison to niece Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1849 July 7, ALS (Box 7)
- Mary F. Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1849 July 23, ALS (Box 7)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Charles C. Harrison 1849 Aug. 22, ALS (Box 7)
- George T. Harrison to sister Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1849 Aug. 27, ALS (Box 7)
- Stephen Olin, President of Wesleyan University to Francis H. Smith, letter of dismissal upon Smith's transfer from Wesleyan University to University of Virginia 1849 Aug. 27, ALS (Box 7)
- Charles Carter Harrison to sister Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1849 Aug. 28, ALS (Box 7)
- Mary Tucker Magill to cousin Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1849 Aug.-Dec., 3 ALS (Box 7)
- Joseph M. Stevens to Caroline E. Harrison 1849 Sept. 3, ALS (Box 7)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1849 Sept. 5, ALS (Box 7)
- Maria Carter Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1849 Sept. 28, ALS (Box 7)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1849 Oct. 4, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel Grove Smith and Ellen (Hamilton) Smith 1849 Oct. 10, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel Grove Smith and Ellen (Hamilton) Smith 1849 Oct. 12, ALS (Box 7)
- Professor George Long to Gessner Harrison 1849 Oct. 17, ALS (Box 7)
- M. Lelia tucker to Maria R. F. Rives 1849 Oct. 18, 26 & 31, 3 ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel Grove Smith 1849 Nov. 17, ALS (Box 7)
- Mary Lelia Tucker to niece Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1849 Nov. 20, ALS (Box 7)
- Otwayanna Carter Owens to her niece Mary Lelia Tucker [1849] Nov. 25, ALS (Box 7)
- M. Lelia tucker to Maria R. F. Rives 1849 Dec. 3, ALS (Box 7)
- Mary Stuart Harrison to M. Lelia Tucker 1849 Dec. 10, ALS (Box 7)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1849 Dec. 13, ALS (Box 7)
- Mr. Thorbecke to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1849 Dec. 18, ALS (Box 7)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Margaret Harrison Stevens 1849 Dec. 21, ALS (Box 7)
- Eliza L. C. Harrison to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1849 Dec. 27, ALS (Box 7)
- Erasmus G. Hamilton to Ellen E. (Hamilton) Smith ca. 1849, ALS (Box 7)
- Powhatan Ellis to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 Jan. 1, ALS (Box 7)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to sister Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 Jan. 10 & Nov. 21, 2 ALS (Box 7)
- Gessner Harrison to Professor Tutwiler 1850 Jan. 14, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith (Mrs. Daniel Smith) 1850 Jan. 17, ALS (Box 7)
- Jane Emmet to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 Jan.-Feb., 2 ALS (Box 7)
- Gessner Harrison to Peachey Rush Harrison 1850 Feb. 14, ALS (Box 7)
- Mary Lelia Tucker to niece Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 Feb. 14, ALS (Box 7)
- (fragment) [?] to Maria [?] 1850 Feb. 14, ALS (Box 7)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1850 Feb. 15, ALS (Box 7)
- John Hunter to [?] 1850 Feb. 19, ALS (Box 7)
- Professor Robley Dunglison to Lelia Tucker 1850 Feb. 24, ALS (Box 7)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker Harrison 1850 Feb. 24, ALS (Box 7)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1850 Feb. 25, ALS (Box 7)
- Ellen Lewis to mar Lelia Tucker 1850 Feb. 28, ALS (Box 7)
- Mary Tucker Magill to cousin Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 Feb.-Dec., 4 ALS (Box 7)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Lelia Tucker 1850 March 2, 2 ALS (Box 7)
- The Reverend R. R. Meade to Mary Leilia Tucker 1850 March 3, ALS (Box 7)
- Maria R. Rives to niece Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 March 5-Dec. 2, 3 ALS (Box 7)
- George Tucker and Louisa A. Tucker to Mary Lelia Tucker 1850 March 5, ALS (Box 7)
- Gessner Harrison to Peachey Rush Harrison 1850 March 10, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1850 March 20, ALS (Box 7)
- Ellen Lewis to Mary Lelia Tucker [1850?] March 21 & 22, 2 ALS (Box 7)
- Francis H. Smith to Ellen E. Smith 1850 April 3, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. smith 1850 April 5, ALS (Box 7)
- Louisa A. Tucker to her step-granddaughter Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 April 12, ALS (Box 7)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1850 April 24, ALS (Box 7)
- Caroline E. Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1850 May 13, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1850 May 27, ALS (Box 7)
- The Reverend R. R. Meade to Mary Leilia Tucker 1850 May 29, ALS (Box 7)
- George Tucker to Daniel Daniel G. Smith 1850 June 9-Dec. 6, ALS (Box 7)
- Caroline E. Harrison to niece Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 June 11, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1850 July 3, ALS (Box 7)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison (Mrs. Peachey Harrison) 1850 July 8, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1850 July 15, ALS (Box 7)
- Gessner Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1850 Aug. 8, ALS (Box 7)
- George T. Harrison to sister Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 Aug. 10, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1850 Aug. 12, ALS (Box 7)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) 1850 Aug. 25, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1850 Aug. 30, ALS (Box 7)
- E. M. Brown to Ellen E. Smith 1850 Sept. 7, ALS (Box 7)
- Mary Stuart Harrison to M. Lelia Tucker 1850 Sept. 9, ALS (Box 7)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker Harrison 1850 Oct. 13, ALS (Box 7)
- Caroline E. Harrison to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 Oct. 14, ALS (Box 7)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1850 Oct. 28, ALS (Box 7)
- Maria C. Broadus to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison (Maria C. Harrison) 1850 Nov. 25, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Summerfield Smith 1850 Nov. 27, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1850 Dec. 2, ALS (Box 7)
- Eliza L. C. Harrison to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 Dec. 3, ALS (Box 7)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1850 Dec. 6 & 9, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel Smith 1850 Dec. 18, ALS (Box 7)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1850 Dec. 20, ALS (Box 7)
- John A. Broadus to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 Dec. 23, ALS (Box 7)
- Mary O. Fleming to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1850 Dec. 28, ALS (Box 7)
- George Tucker to Mary Stuart Harrison 1850 Dec. 29, ALS (Box 7)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1850 Dec. 30, ALS (Box 7)
- Lucy Gilmer to Mary Lelia Tucker ca. 1850, ALS (Box 7)
- Ann E. T. Magill to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison ca. 1850, ALS (Box 7)
- Ann E. T. Magill to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison ca. 1850, ALS (Box 7)
- Ann E. T. Magill to Mary Lelia Tucker ca. 1850, ALS (Box 7)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Harrison 1851 Jan. 1, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1851 Jan. 2 & 8, 2 ALS (Box 7)
- Gessner Harrison to daughter Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1851 Jan. 8, ALS (Box 7)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker Harrison 1851 Jan. 9, ALS (Box 7)
- Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1851 Jan. 13, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1851 Jan. 17, ALS (Box 7)
- Joseph M. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens 1851 Jan. 17, ALS (Box 7)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1851 Jan. 20, ALS (Box 7)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1851 Jan. 22, ALS (Box 7)
- Gessner Harrison to Charles Carter Harrison 1851 Jan. 25, ALS (Box 7)
- Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus to Mary Jane Harrison 1851 Feb. 5, ALS (Box 7)
- Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus to Mary Jane Harrison 1851 Feb. 5, ALS (Box 7)
- Eliza L. C. Harrison to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1851 Feb. 12-July 20, 6 ALS (Box 7)
- Mary S. (Harrison) Smith to sister Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1851 Feb. 13-Sept. 8, 10 ALS (Box 7)
- Lucy (Stevens) Clarks to Mrs. Margaret Stevens 1851 Feb. 14, ALS (Box 7)
- Joseph M. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens 1851 Feb. 14, ALS (Box 7)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1851 Feb. 26, ALS (Box 7)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1851 March 1, ALS (Box 7)
- Maria R. Rives to niece Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1851 March 3-Aug. 6, 5 ALS (Box 7)
- Henry William Harrison to sister [Maria] Broadus and brother George [Harrison] 1851 March 6, ALS (Box 7)
- Daniel G. Smith to his son Francis H. Smith 1851 March 12, ALS (Box 7)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. (Harrison) Stevens 1851 March 14, ALS (Box 7)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. (Harrison) Stevens (1851 March 15?], ALS (Box 8)
- Mary Tucker Magill to cousin Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1851 March 17, ALS (Box 8)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1851 March 19, ALS (Box 8)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1851 March 25, ALS (Box 8)
- Gessner Harrison Broadus to Charles Carter Harrison 1851 March 29, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus to Mary Jane Harrison 1851 April 1, ALS (Box 8)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallce) to Mary Jane Harrison 1851 April 14, ALS (Box 8)
- George Tucker to Mary Stuart Harrison 1851 April 20, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus to Mary Stuart Harrison 1851 April 28, ALS (Box 8)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1851 [May], ALS (Box 8)
- Francis H. Smith to Daniel Grove Smith 1851 May 9, ALS (Box 8)
- Louise A. Tucker to her step-granddaughter Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1851 May 12, ALS (Box 8)
- jane Emmet to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1851 May 15, ALS (Box 8)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1851 May 19, ALS (Box 8)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Dr. Gessner Harrison 1851 May 23, ALS (Box 8)
- Gessner Harrison to Mray (Stewart) Harrison 1851 May 25, ALS (Box 8)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1851 May 26 & 28, ALS (Box 8)
- [Mrs. Peachey Rush Harrison] to Mary Stuart Harrison 1851 June 6, ALS (Box 8)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker Harrison 1851 June 9, ALS (Box 8)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1851 June 11, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria C. Broadus to Maria R. F. Rives 1851 June 16, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1851 July 1, ALS (Box 8)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1851 July 2, ALS (Box 8)
- I. S. David to Francis H. Smith 1851 July 9, (printed letter) (Box 8)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1851 July 14, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1851 July 21, ALS (Box 8)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1851 Aug. 22, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1851 Aug. 24, ALS (Box 8)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1851 Aug. 20; Sept. 2, 2 ALS (Box 8)
- Transcript of letter and newsclipping, Peachey Harrison to Mrs. Rives 1851 Sept. 5, ALS (Box 8)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1851 Sept. 24, ALS (Box 8)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker Harrison 1851 Oct. 4, ALS (Box 8)
- Mary Jane Harrison to niece Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1851 Oct. 8, ALS (Box 8)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1851 Oct. 20, ALS (Box 8)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. (Harrison) Stevens 1851 Oct. 29; Nov. 3, 2 ALS (Box 8)
- Maria C. Broadus to Mary Jane Harrison 1851 Nov. 10, ALS (Box 8)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker Harrison 1851 Nov. 23; Dec. 11, 2 ALS (Box 8)
- Margaret Harrison Stevens to William G. Stevens 1851 Dec. 13, ALS (Box 8)
- M. G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1851 Dec. 16, ALS (Box 8)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker Harrison 1851 Dec. 17, ALS (Box 8)
- ca. 1851 Francis H. Smith to Ellen E. Smith, ALS (Box 8)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Harrison ca. 1851, ANS and ALS (Box 8)
- Betsy I. Tutt to Eliza L. C. Tucker Harrison [ante. 1852] Sept. 27, ALS (Box 8)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1852 Jan. 3, ALS (Box 8)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker Harrison 1852 Jan. 5, ALS (Box 8)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1852 Jan. 11, ALS (Box 8)
- Eliza P. and M. G. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1852 Jan. 12, ALS (Box 8)
- Edward Buckey Smith to Ellen E. Smith (Mrs. Daniel G. Smith) 1852 Jan. 20, ALS (Box 8)
- Margaret H. Stevens to William G. Stevens 1852 Jan. 20 & 27, 2 ALS (Box 8)
- William G. Stevens to Mary Jane Harrison 1852 Feb. 5, ALS (Box 8)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallce) to William G. Stevens 1852 [Feb. 7], ALS (Box 8)
- Lucy (Stevens) Clarks to brother [William G. Stevens] 1852 Feb. 10, ALS (Box 8)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1852 Feb. 13, ALS (Box 8)
- Matthew Gill Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1852 Feb. 19, ALS (Box 8)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker Harrison [1852] Feb. 24, ALS (Box 8)
- Lucy Cocke to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1852 Feb., ALS (Box 8)
- Mary Stuart Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1852 March 1, ALS (Box 8)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens 1852 March 11, ALS (Box 8)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1852 March 12, ALS (Box 8)
- Margaret H. Stevens to William G. Stevens 1852 March 15, ALS (Box 8)
- Caroline E. Harrison to Mary Stuart Harrison 1852 March 16, ALS (Box 8)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker [1852] March 18, ALS (Box 8)
- Gessner Harrison to Peachey Rush Harrison 1852 April 5, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1852 April 8, ALS (Box 8)
- John H. Stevens to William G. Stevens 1852 April 15, ALS (Box 8)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens 1852 April 21, ALS (Box 8)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1852 May 3, ALS (Box 8)
- Margaret Harrison Stevens to William G. Stevens 1852 May 4, ALS (Box 8)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens 1852 May 8, ALS (Box 8)
- Summerfield Smith to Francis H. Smith 1852 May 14, ALS (Box 8)
- Mary Stuart Harrison to Francis H. Smith 1852 May 17, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1852 May 17, ALS (Box 8)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker 1852 May 20, ALS (Box 8)
- Julia C. Langhorne to Mary [Stuart] Harrison 1852 May 21, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1852 May 22, ALS (Box 8)
- Matthew Gill Hamilton to Ellen Smith 1852 May 31, ALS (Box 8)
- Margaret Harrison Stevens to William G. Stevens 1852 May 31, ALS (Box 8)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary J. Harrison 1852 June 3, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1852 June 5, ALS (Box 8)
- Mary F. Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1852 June 10, ALS (Box 8)
- Matthew Gill Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1852 June 11, ALS (Box 8)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker 1852 June 13, ALS (Box 8)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Mary Jane Harrison 1852 June 18, ALS (Box 8)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1852 June 20, ALS (Box 8)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis and Edward Smith 1852 June 21, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1852 July 5, ALS (Box 8)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Harrison 1852 July 6, ALS (Box 8)
- Matthew Gill Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1852 July 7, ALS (Box 8)
- Albert S. Hunt to Francis H. Smith 1852 July 7, ALS (Box 8)
- Mary Stuart Harrison to Francis H. Smith 1852 July 10, ALS (Box 8)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Harrison 1852 July 21, ALS (Box 8)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Dr. Gessner Harrison 1852 July 23, ALS (Box 8)
- Mary Stuart Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1852 Aug. 21, ALS (Box 8)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1852 Aug. 28, ALS (Box 8)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Margaret Harrison Stevens 1852 Sept. 1, ALS (Box 8)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Caroline E. Harrison 1852 Sept. 2, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus to John Broadus 1852 Sept. 21, ALS (Box 8)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1852 Sept. 23, ALS (Box 8)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker 1852 Sept. 29, ALS (Box 8)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1852 Oct. 1, ALS (Box 8)
- Mary F. Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison (MRs. Peachey Rush Harrison) (Mrs. Peachey Harrison) 1852 Oct. 11, ALS (Box 8)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1852 Oct. 11, ALS (Box 8)
- Maria C. Broadus to Mary Jane Harrison 1852 Oct. 18, 2 ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1852 Oct. 18, ALS (Box 9)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. Tucker [1852] Oct. 27; Nov. 1, 2 ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel Grove Smith to Francis H. Smith 1852 Nov. 11, ALS (Box 9)
- Margaret Harrison Stevens to Mary (Stewart) Harrison (Mrs. Peachey Harrison) 1852 Nov. 30, ALS (Box 9)
- Francis H. Smith to Ellen E. Smith 1852 Dec. 2, ALS (Box 9)
- E. R. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1852 Dec. 15, ALS (Box 9)
- Caroline E. Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1852 Dec. 16, ALS (Box 9)
- Francis H. Smith to Daniel G. Smith 1852 Dec. 28, ALS (Box 9)
- Edward Buckey Smith to Ellen E. Smith 1852 Dec. 29, ALS (Box 9)
- Margaret H. Stevens to William G. Stevens [1852], ALS (Box 9)
- Mary F. Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison [1852], ALS (Box 9)
- Mary F. Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison [1852], ALS (Box 9)